DAVID BOERM

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

PHONE

325.232.4491

EMAIL

davidboerm@gmail.com

SKILLS

MongoDB

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Express.js

.

React

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Node.js

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

• • • • •

Git

• • • • 0

Front End Development

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Adobe Photoshop

• • • •

Adobe Illustrator

• • • • •

Adobe XD

• • • • • •

PROFILE

Recent SMU full stack web development bootcamp graduate with skills including: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Bulma, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Express, mySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, and React. I plan to leverage additional skills from my previous graphic design career to also create solid applications with style and visual appeal as well. Additionally, as a 20-year military veteran, I have a breadth of experience ranging from being the lead subject matter expert for my area of work, leading training sessions, extensive leadership, and cooperative action.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Graphic Designer, Fastsigns

Dallas

Sep 2019 — Mar 2020

- Created commercial print layouts for a wide variety of businesses, utilizing current Adobe creative apps including Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Operated and maintained large format printers, vinyl cutting machines, as well as file generation for CNC and laser routers.
- Assisted with sign assembly, storefront vinyl application, and shop organization.

Division Manager, Micro Precision Calibration

Austin

Jun 2018 — Jun 2019

- Managed accredited calibration laboratory, including three calibration technicians, shipping/receiving clerk, and office manager.
- Performed over \$800K in calibration sales, 140% increase from previous year
- Maintained lab facility, equipment, supplies, and all utility contract services

Avionics Maintenance Personnel Manager, U. S. Air Force

Abilene

Jan 1998 — Feb 2018

- Led over 200 C-130J maintenance personnel comprised of 6 specialties for 14 aircraft valued at \$900M
- Coordinated, planned, and directed deployments, maintenance recovery teams, training exercises, and all other tasked missions

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Graphic Design, The Art Institutes

2009 — 2013

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Southern Methodist University

Dallas